Finding aid of the Herbert Hutchinson Brimley Photograph Collection, 1880-1977 PHC.42
State Archives of North Carolina
- Marine Life, PhC.42.MarineLife; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sperm whale, Wrightsville Beach, NC, 1928. (3n), PhC.42.Bx17.MarineLife.F2-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fiddler crabs, Southport, NC, 1913. (n), PhC.42.Bx17.MarineLife.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Military, PhC.42.Military; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Davis, Onslow Co., NC, ca. 1940s. (4), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Davis, Onslow Co., NC, ca. 1940s. (4), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Davis, Onslow Co., NC, ca. 1940s. (4), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Davis, Onslow Co., NC, ca. 1940s. (4), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - British Sailor's Rest Camp, Crabtree Park, Wake Co., NC, 1941. (17), PhC.42.Bx17.Military.F2-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Grist Mills, PhC.42.MillsGrist; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old Water Mill, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1910., PhC.42.Bx17.MillsGrist.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old time mountain mill, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1910., PhC.42.Bx17.MillsGrist.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Modern mountain mill, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1910., PhC.42.Bx17.MillsGrist.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Minerals, PhC.42.Minerals; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - An Emerald Crystal, Alexander Co., NC, ca. 1910., PhC.42.Bx17.Minerals.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Mines and Mining, PhC.42.MinesMining; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Neverson Granite Quarry, Wilson Co., NC, 1930, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F10-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Neverson Granite Quarry, Wilson Co., NC, 1930, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F10-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Neverson Granite Quarry, Wilson Co., NC, 1930, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F10-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sevier Marble Quarry, McDowell Co., NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F10-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cranberry, NC Iron Mine, Avery Co., NC, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F10-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Harris Clay Co., Spruce Pine, NC, 1927. (1)(6n), PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F10-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Manganese Oxide Deposit, Globe, NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F10-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Silver Family at Mica Mine Site 26 Nov, 1942 Franklin Co, NC, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lundy Pit, Harris Clay Co., Spruce Pine, NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cranberry, NC Iron Mine, Avery Co., NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lundy Pit, Harris Clay Co., Spruce Pine, NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Staley Gearhardt Pyrophylite Mine, Randolph Co., NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Staley Gearhardt Pyrophylite Mine, Randolph Co., NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Staley Gearhardt Pyrophylite Mine, Randolph Co., NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - N.G. Smith Co. Pit, Spruce Pine, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - N.G. Smith Co. Pit, Spruce Pine, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - White Mine Marble Quarry, Cherokee Co., NC, 1927. (10), PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - White Mine Marble Quarry, Cherokee Co., NC, 1927. (10), PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F11-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Clay Pit in Spruce Pine 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cranberry, NC Iron mining village, Avery Co., NC, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F12-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - McKinney Feldspar Mine, Little Switzerland, NC, 1931, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F12-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - McKinney Feldspar Mine, Little Switzerland, NC, 1931, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F12-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - McKinney Feldspar Mine, Little Switzerland, NC, 1931, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F12-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Carolina Coal Co., Chatham Co., NC, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F12-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Carolina Coal Co., Chatham Co., NC, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F12-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sevier Quarry, McDowell Co., NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F12-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Proposed Quarry Site, Rockingham Co., NC, ca. 1920s. (8n), PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F12-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - McKinney Mine (Feldspar) in Little Switzerland During Blast- 1800 lbs dynamite 9/5 '31, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - McKinney Mine just after blast 9/5 '31 messrs Collburn (B.S.), Ricker, Burton, Dr. Shaler, etc., PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Primitive Chilean Mill Deraska, Chaser, or Miller Made of Pink Granite at Old Rimmer Gold Mine 1 mile SE of Granite Quarry Rowan Co, NC very heavy but very attractive exhibit connected with mining industry Aug. 24 '24, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F1-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - McKinney Mine just after blast 9/5 '31, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F1-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - McKinney Mine 9/5 '31, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F1-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica, Feldspar, and Quartz, Sprunt Hill Farm, Wake Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F2-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica Prospects, Alga Mine, Franklin Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F3-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica Prospects, Alga Mine, Franklin Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F3-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica Prospects, Alga Mine, Franklin Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F3-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica Prospects, Alga Mine, Franklin Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F3-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica Prospects, Alga Mine, Franklin Co., NC, 1942, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F3-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Aluminum Factories, Badin, NC, ca. 1940. (3) (4n), PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F3-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Water Wheel Iron Foundry, Hilton's Creek, Ashe Co., NC, ca. 1890, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F4-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Water Wheel Iron Foundry, Hilton's Creek, Ashe Co., NC, ca. 1890, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F4-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Carolina Coal Co- Coal Glen Chatham Co, NC Feb- before explosion of 27 may, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F4-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Carolina Coal Co- Coal Glen Chatham Co, NC Feb- before explosion of 27 may, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F4-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Carolina Coal Co- Coal Glen Chatham Co, NC Feb- before explosion of 27 may, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F4-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fletcher Limestone Quarry Co Buncombe Co 8 Nov. '41, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F4-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cammock Coal Mine 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F4-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cammock Coal Mine 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F4-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sevier Marble Quarry, McDowell Co., NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F5-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sevier Marble Quarry, McDowell Co., NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F5-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Barden Brick and Tile Co., Sanford, NC, 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F5-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Barden Brick and Tile Co., Sanford, NC, 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F5-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Barden Brick and Tile Co., Sanford, NC, 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F5-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mica Plant, Plumtree, NC, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F5-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cranberry, NC, iron mining village, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F5-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Quarry site, Rockingham Co., NC, ca. 1920s., PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F5-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Marble Quarry, Cherokee Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old Chilean Mill, Cold Hill, NC, 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F7-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old Chilean Mill, Cold Hill, NC, 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F7-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Quarry, Willets, NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F7-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Harris Granite Co. Quarry, 1926. (1) (3n), PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F7-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Harris Granite Co., Pelham Quarry, Caswell Co., NC, 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F8-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Harris Granite Co., Pelham Quarry, Caswell Co., NC, 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F8-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Norman G. Smith Co. Flotation Plant, Spruce Pine, NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F8-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Norman G. Smith Co. Flotation Plant, Spruce Pine, NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F8-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Norman G. Smith Co. Flotation Plant, Spruce Pine, NC, 1927, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F8-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Stacey Building Stone Quarry, Rockingham Co., NC, 1926. (3)(7n), PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F9-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Plumtree Mill and Grinding Co, Tar Heel Mica Co., Avery Co., NC, 1925, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F9-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Quarry, Harris Granite Co., 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F9-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Quarry, Harris Granite Co., 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F9-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Quarry, Harris Granite Co., 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F9-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Quarry, Harris Granite Co., 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F9-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Quarry, Harris Granite Co., 1926, PhC.42.Bx18.MinesMining.F9-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Miscellaneous, PhC.42.Misc; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Magnolia Gardens, Charleston, SC, 1923. (11), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F1-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Lost Colony" theatrical stage, ca. 1930s., PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Views of California and Mexico., PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F3-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Views of California and Mexico., PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F3-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Views of California and Mexico., PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F3-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Views of California and Mexico., PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F3-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Views of California and Mexico., PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F3-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Views of California and Mexico., PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F3-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Views of California and Mexico., PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F3-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting catch, Sampson Co., NC, ca. 1900, PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F4-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Child with St. Bernard Dog, Will Robbins Home, Hillsboro St., Raleigh, NC, ca. 1900s, PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F4-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Child with St. Bernard Dog, Will Robbins Home, Hillsboro St., Raleigh, NC, ca. 1900s, PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F4-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Flags atop the Agriculture Building, Raleigh, NC, 1967. (5), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F4-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Patrol shacks, Camp Craggy, Wake Co., NC, ca. 1940, PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F4-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-21; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-22; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-23; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-24; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-25; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-26; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-27; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-28; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-29; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-30; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-31; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-32; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-33; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-34; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-35; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-36; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-37; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-38; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-39; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-40; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-41; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-42; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-43; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-44; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-45; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-46; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-47; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-48; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-49; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Souvenir photo set of World War I scenes, France and Germany, ca. 1920. (60), PhC.42.Bx18.Misc.F5-50; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946